(Bernadette:)Want to pause the video game
and help me clean up?
(Howard:)I am cleaning up.
(Howard:)Look at the mess the Joker
made of Gotham City.
(Bernadette:)Come on, it's your friend
who's coming to stay here.
(Howard:)Raj grew up in India.
(Howard:)Trust me, he's seen worse.
(Bernadette:)Howie.
(Howard:)I promise I'll help out
the rest of the week.
(Bernadette:)The rest of the week?
(Bernadette:)You said it was just
going to be a night or two.
(Howard:)Yeah, but if I told you a week,
would you have said yes?
-No!
-Then you left me no choice.
(Bernadette:)I love Raj, but that's
a long time for a house guest.
(Amy:)I know,
but they're tenting his building.
(Howard:)He can't find a hotel
he likes that allows dogs.
(Bernadette:)-He's bringing Cinnamon?
-For a whole week!
(Howard:)The nerve of some people.
(Sheldon:)Here comes
the Embarrassment Express.
(Sheldon:)With stops at Fraudville...
...WonderBIunderberg...
(Sheldon:)...and Kansas City.